<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MMDD Methodology News</title>
    <description>Latest news and updates from the Micromanaged Driven Development framework</description>
    <link>https://mmdd.dev</link>
    <atom:link href="https://mmdd.dev/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <managingEditor>team@mmdd.dev (MMDD Team)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@mmdd.dev (MMDD Team)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:44:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>MMDD Vite RSS Plugin</generator>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Micromanaged Driven Development v2.0]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the release of MMDD Version 2! This release focuses on organizational improvements, better consistency, and streamlined adoption. What's New: Improved file organization with renamed core principles file (00_mdd.md → 00_mmdd.md), enhanced documentation with updated internal references, and project cleanup removing unimplemented units. The methodology now shows 85% completion status with core principles, templates, and real-world validation complete. Getting Started: New users can download the latest principles with `curl -O https://mmdd.dev/00_mmdd.md`. Existing users should update references from 00_mdd.md to 00_mmdd.md and review the updated principles.]]></description>
      <link>https://github.com/robertoallende/micromanaged-driven-development/discussions/2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mmdd-micromanaged-driven-development-v2-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[CodeRipple: AWS Lambda Hackathon 2025 Project Delivery]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[CodeRipple demonstrates MMDD in action - an automated code analysis pipeline built 100% with AI assistance using systematic documentation and controlled orchestration. The project transforms commit events into comprehensive code insights through serverless architecture. Built using Micromanaged Driven Development, CodeRipple validates the methodology's effectiveness for complex AI-assisted development. Every architectural decision, service integration, and technical challenge was systematically documented and AI-orchestrated through the MMDD methodology.]]></description>
      <link>https://github.com/robertoallende/coderipple</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mmdd-coderipple--aws-lambda-hackathon-2025-project-deli</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Code with AI: Micromanagement is all you need]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An in-depth article exploring how systematic micromanagement transforms AI from an unpredictable assistant into a controlled, reliable development partner. Roberto Allende shares the story behind MMDD, from the initial frustration with AI's unpredictability to developing a methodology that maintains control through granular oversight, documentation, and iterative refinement of every AI suggestion.]]></description>
      <link>https://builder.aws.com/content/2y6nQgj1FVuaJIn9rFLThIslwaJ/code-with-ai-micromanagement-is-all-you-need</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mmdd-code-with-ai--micromanagement-is-all-you-need</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[MMDD Methodology Version 1 Released]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Micromanaged Driven Development (MMDD) version 1 is now available. This development methodology uses systematic documentation to control AI-assisted software development through granular task breakdown and chronological tracking. The methodology provides structured templates for project organization, unit-based development tracking, and comprehensive AI interaction documentation to maintain control and visibility in AI-assisted development workflows.]]></description>
      <link>https://github.com/robertoallende/micromanaged-driven-development</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mmdd-mmdd-methodology-version-1-released</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>